他在观看演习啊
He's watching the maneuvers.
警署总督呢？
And the Police Commissioner?
我知道了，他在监视维利·勃兰特
I see. He's watching Willy Brandt.
那警察局谁管？
So who's minding the store?
打到伯恩那边去了吗？
What about the call to Bonn?
大使回华盛顿参加咨询会去了？
Our ambassador is back in Washington for consulation?
进来，进来，我等会跟你说
Come in, come in. I'll be right with you.
打到华盛顿的国务院去
Get me Washington, the State Department...
谁接都行
whoever answers
迪安·拉斯克，迪安·艾奇逊，是个叫迪安的都行
Dean Rusk, Dean Acheson, Dean
如果那边也没人接
And if you have no luck there...
就打给乔治亚州的塔尔马吉参议员
get me Senator Talmadge of Georgia.
如果他也不在，就试试打给国家广播公司的亨特利和布林克利
If he isn't in, try Huntley
斯嘉丽！
Scarlett!
你这么激动干嘛？
What's all the excitement?
哦，没事
Oh, nothing.
你刚才把我们都吓死了！
You just scared the hell out of us!
你还好吗？
You all right?